Hello everyone, I am Celia. Today, Andy and I will introduce you to the new features of Closet 2024.0.
This time, the new features mainly include nine aspects, namely the main functions, documents, 2D, 3D, virtual models, materials, modes, rendering, and Closet.
This live broadcast is divided into two stages. In the first half, I will introduce the first four aspects to you, and the latter part will be explained by Andy.
Let's start today's introduction.
First of all, I will introduce the main features of the update.
The first is about account collection.
From the 2024 version, individual users can now visit all products of Closet through a collection account.
The collection account means that users can use all services and software provided by Closet with no need to register individually using the individual e-mail account.
When you log in using the collection account,
you will use your e-mail to automatically log in to all Closet related services, including Closet software, Closet platform, Connect Business, Marvelous Designer, and Genie, instead of logging in through your user ID.
Using the collection account can make your work process smoother.
In addition, by using the Closet account, you can greatly reduce the risk of multi-account management and easily manage and update account information on a page.
Even if the account is collected,
all data, assets, and subscriptions in the existing account will remain unchanged.
You can continue to download and use software licenses and purchase projects.
Currently, the collection account is only used for individual users.
Enterprise users do not need to take any additional operations.
For new users, the collection account will be automatically created when they register.
Next, let's take a look at the operation process of the collection account of existing users.
For existing users,
the current account will be merged according to your registered e-mail address.
When logging in from the Closet software,
use the existing license ID and password to log in to the login window.
At this time, a collection account creation window will appear.
Click the OK button to enter the Closet login page.
Click Create Account to complete the mobile phone number verification and agree to the terms and conditions.
You will use the Closet license ID and password you entered.
You will use the Closet license ID and password you entered to create a collection account.
If you have registered a Closet account using the same e-mail address,
Closet will automatically match the e-mail address and convert it into a unified collection account.
If Closet does not use the account registered with the same e-mail address,
it will create a Closet account and convert it into a collection account.
If you use the Closet software and Closet at the same time,
but use different e-mail addresses,
in this case, you can connect to the e-mail account you chose.
If you integrate the existing Closet account with the Closet account,
you can use the files stored and downloaded in the account in the original way.
If you want to connect to the Closet account you are using,
you can contact us to help you merge the e-mail address related to your account.
In the future, we will also develop this feature so that users can directly connect.
After completing the conversion of the collection account,
you can automatically log into the Closet software by saving the ID password as before.
In addition, you can also create a collection account for existing users on the Closet official website.
Visit the Closet official website and click the Login button.
Log in with your existing Closet ID password.
At this time, the window that will create and generate your collection account will appear.
Click the Confirm button.
Click the
Once the collection account is digitized,
It is taken to the Closet account.
When entering to the Closet login window,
complete the collection account.
After the update of the 2024 version, you only need to perform the above operations when you first connect and set up the integrated account, and after the conversion is complete, there will be no more account integrated
Finally, if you want to use an e-mail account, you must use the same e-mail address in all cloud services
If you have any questions, you can check the help center website related to the integrated account in the video description
Using the integrated account, you will cooperate with all cloud services and easily manage your account information on one page
We have been researching and developing to change the appearance and performance of cloud-based needle products
Before that, we must create various stickers manually based on the texture or material to express the needle structure
From the new version, the material type of the material has been added the option of needle clothing, which will start from the structure of the needle product to help us show the appearance of the needle product that is more realistic
Since the needle organization is expressed by the grid, it is very natural to simulate
Select a piece of needle in the software
In the bottom attribute editor, an option of needle clothing has been added in the material type
Add the material type to change to needle clothing
At this time, the attribute editor will also be adjusted to the option of needle clothing used in the new
And after modifying the settings, you can check the change effect in the 3D window
First of all, we can switch between different preset needles
We can switch between different preset needles
Now we prepare the first preset needles
In order to truly show the texture of the needle and thread, the surface of the needle and thread is also applied to the hair line sticker.
If you delete the hair line sticker, you can see that the shadow of the edge thread will become lighter.
Ctrl-Z can be withdrawn.
In addition, you can also set the number of threads used on each bone thread.
You can set the value between 1 and 6.
And below you can see that the colors of each bone thread can be set.
Click on the color card on the right to set different colors for each bone thread.
In order to naturally express the seam of the needle and thread clothing, we use the option of creating a seam by default.
By creating a thread line on the sewing line connected to the sewing line and the outside of the board,
the needle and thread of the whole clothing can be naturally realized.
The length of the seam curve can be used to control the seam length beyond the extension to the board.
The lower the number, the shorter the seam length, and the longer the length of the needle and thread.
If the seam curve is reduced under the use of the deep seam option, the seam line and the outside of the board will become even.
The needle and thread will be turned to the opposite side of the board.
As mentioned earlier, the needle and thread clothing has a grid structure, so it will affect 3D operation and rendering speed.
Especially the higher the density of the embroidery, the more the grid is calculated, the greater the impact on speed.
Therefore, after completing the attribute of the needle and thread clothing, you can use the needle and thread clothing to control the speed in the 3D window.
Next, we will pre-use the fabric made by the needle and thread clothing preset to be applied to the clothes separately.
Open the rendering to see the rendering result.
You can see that the performance of the needle and thread clothing is now more natural and rich than before.
In addition to needle and thread clothing, you can also use the needle and thread clothing to control the speed in the 3D window.
You can also use the needle and thread clothing to control the speed in the 3D window.
Finally, needle and thread clothing is a material that can only be used in clothes, so it is difficult to extract it as an external expansion format such as OBJ, FBX, or GLTF, or to store it as an image.
Therefore, you can store the needle and thread clothing you process as a project file, or store the fabric as a ZFAB file to store it.
By using this technology, the visual effect of needle and thread clothing has been greatly improved.
You can easily create more realistic needle and thread fabrics by adjusting the preset and setting of various needle and thread clothing.
If you have any thoughts or opinions on needle and thread clothing, please scan the QR code.
Your feedback will further help us optimize the needle and thread clothing function.
From the 2024.0 version, the user interface of CLOUD starts to update.
The new version of the interface becomes more intuitive and efficient, and the user experience is improved.
First is the overall update of the CLOUD color system.
In general, the overall color and text of this software have been updated.
First is the update of the file opening dialogue box.
Here, the DXF file is used as an example.
In the DXF window, the selected frame is displayed in blue, which is more intuitive and easy to understand.
In the main menu, when the mouse is stopped on the required content, not only the file name of the menu can be seen, but also the menu itself will show more intuitively.
In addition, the icon design in the software has become clearer and easier to distinguish visually.
This time, the icon in the 2D tool bar, 3D tool bar and the object window have been updated.
Also, the icon in the visually-productive tool tab is divided into open and save icons on the right Sylphid.
The display of the field card and the side view now is also clearer.
The update has also optimized the icon layout of the 2D and 3D window.
In the new version, users can only use the corresponding icon to open or close each topic,
so it is difficult to determine which display view in the menu is activated or stopped.
After the new version is improved, users can now directly control the display status of 3D and 2D viewing views.
Similarly, in the upper left corner of the 3D and 2D window, you can see the icon that displays the switch.
If there is only one menu in each topic, you can directly click on the icon to switch the switch.
When there are multiple options, when you stop the mouse on the required menu,
you will see a re-selected icon and the desired option name,
which is convenient for you to check the switch status of the display mode.
In the later version,
the interface design will continue to improve.
Please look forward to the subsequent updates.
The following is an update on file display.
Starting from the 2024 version,
files such as ZP-RJ project files, ZP-AC clothing files, AVT virtual models,
and clothes, accessories, accessories, etc. are now displayed in the folder.
You can see that after the software update,
ZP-RJ project files will be displayed from the software picture.
The new software icon will appear in the lower right corner of the filter.
Here we open a project file of Cloud ZP-RJ.
Find the file storage project in the software and save it again.
Back to the folder, you can see that the new version will still store ZP-RJ project files and PNG filters.
At this time, ZP-RJ project files will also display in the form of filters.
The new software icon will appear in the lower right corner of the filter.
Therefore, when you share files afterwards,
you do not need to send PNG filters at the same time,
and you can also preview the files.
The following is an update on 2D related functions.
First of all, in the new version,
you can add custom 2D measurements to the stickers.
When measuring the position of the stickers,
you usually need to measure the distance between them and the specific points on the board.
Now you can do it through the new function.
First, select the adjustment sticker tool.
Right-click on the sticker.
Find the custom 2D measurement tool.
Then select the point you want to refer to on the outside of the board.
Here we can click on the high point on the board.
After adding custom 2D measurements,
it will display at the bottom of the 2D measurement of the attribute editor.
You can enter its name here.
Next to the name,
you can also display or hide the measurement value through the review window.
Click on the small trash can icon to delete the custom 2D measurement value.
You can also measure the distance between the sticker below to the left side and the bottom.
Use the adjustment sticker tool.
Right-click on the sticker.
Select custom 2D measurement.
Then, on the outside of the board,
confirm the point you want to measure.
In the attribute editor,
you can re-name the measurement value.
If you have a horse-drawn costume,
you can check the measurement value of each horse-drawn size by changing the size of the horse.
In general,
this tool can help you to match the sticker measurement value with the specific point of the board.
From the new version,
you can easily replace the board outline.
The new replacement line function in the 2D window
can easily replace one or more lines into another line in the board.
For example,
I will use this chain store as an example.
Now all the boards of this suit are finished.
Next, we will modify the board.
For example,
here we modify one side of the sleeve.
The other side of the line can use the replacement line function to maintain the shape matching.
Select the edit board tool.
And right-click on the line you just modified.
In the menu,
select copy.
Then,
on the other side of the sleeve,
right-click again.
In the pop-up menu,
select the replacement line section.
At this time,
you can see that
the line section that is about to be replaced on the board
will be previewed in yellow.
At the same time,
the window of the replacement line section will pop up.
Here are some options to choose from.
First,
select the option to copy one or more lines
that are different from the length of the replacement line section.
Since the two sides of the sleeve have the same length,
we will keep the start direction here,
without making any changes.
At the bottom,
there are two options,
vertical rotation and horizontal rotation.
Select the option.
The line section will rotate in the same direction according to the vertical axis and the horizontal axis.
These two options can be selected separately or together.
The specific direction depends on the line section you want to replace.
Here,
I want the two sides of the sleeve to be symmetrical.
You can see that
the bent part of the line section is below.
Therefore,
select the horizontal rotation,
and turn the bent part up.
According to the preview,
we also need to select the option of vertical rotation.
Through this method,
we can adjust the shape of the sleeve.
After the selection is complete,
click OK to modify the application.
Open the simulation,
and you can see the result in 3D.
You can see the result in 3D.
Similarly,
you can also replace multiple lines.
For example,
we can modify its shape.
After the modification,
we can use the function of replacing the line section
to keep the front and the collar matching.
Press the Shift key
to select all the lines that need to match the front and the collar.
Then,
on the line section,
right-click to select the line section to replace.
In the face of the line section with different lengths of replacement,
we can use the direction option
to select how to assign a new measurement value.
When selecting the Start option,
we can see that
the line section is only increased downwards at the bottom,
and will not affect the shoulder line of the panel.
Switching to both ends of the BOSE,
it will move two sides of the BOSE.
In this way,
you can see that
the line section is only increased downwards at the bottom,
and will not affect the shoulder line of the panel.
However,
the line section will move two ends of the BOSE,
and distribute a new measurement value evenly.
End
The direction and the starting direction are the opposite.
Please move the point to adjust the length.
Here,
the starting and ending directions depend on how the panel is created,
and may change depending on the panel.
For the current situation,
we select Start,
and do not need to select the flip option.
After clicking OK,
we can see
all the important lines have been replaced, and you can also see the internal lines in the board,
because they are connected to the outside of the board, so they will move correctly to the new outside of the board.
After the modification is complete, we can open the simulation to see the results.
In general, using the new function of replacing lines can make it more convenient and accurate to change the outside of the board.
From the new version, we have added the function of converting multiple lines to straight lines.
In the 2D window, select the tool to edit the lines.
On the board, select the lines to be converted.
On the selected lines, right-click to convert them all to straight lines.
Using this tool can help us very well to edit and adjust the board.
In addition, in the 2D vertical menu,
we have added the option to display or hide the angle of the board.
In the 2D vertical menu,
the fourth button in the information display shows the angle.
Click to activate it to see the angle of the board.
Since the last version, the 2D window has added the option to display and hide the shrinkage.
In order to make these information more suitable for production,
we can now arrange the board according to the shrinkage.
For example, let's use this jeans.
After washing the jeans, the shrinkage rate reaches 80%.
Ctrl-A to select all the boards.
Then change the horizontal shrinkage rate to 80% in the property editor.
Enter the hard-to-sew mode.
You can see that the board is now in the actual size.
In the property editor, there are two options in the board size.
The actual size and the shrinkage rate.
Select the shrinkage rate.
You can see that the shrinkage board is displayed in the hard-to-sew editor.
Click to arrange.
After arranging, we can also switch to the actual size at any time to rearrange.
Return to the simulation mode.
On the other hand, we can also stretch the board.
For example, change the horizontal shrinkage rate to 120%.
Repeat the process just now to arrange the enlarged board.
Next is the update about 3D.
First of all, it is related to the optimization of grid type.
The grid type of optimized board is optimized by using the automatic overlap algorithm.
First of all, the 3D grid helps us build 3D clothing and board.
Cloud supports two grid types.
Triangle grid and quadrilateral grid.
Triangle grid shows the shape of the triangle.
Quadrilateral grid shows the shape of the quadrilateral.
First of all, the 3D window and the 2D window are changed to grid display.
When selecting the version, we can find the grid type at the bottom of the parameter editor.
Grid type settings.
Here are two options, triangle and quadrilateral.
The quadrilateral grid algorithm has been optimized in the 2024.0 version, so it is renamed quadrilateral optimization.
When choosing quadrilateral optimization, you can see that
the grid appearance of the selected version in the 3D and 2D windows has been changed to quadrilateral grid.
In the 3D window, right-click on the board.
We can also see that an option has been added to the menu.
Here you can also change the grid type.
After the grid type has been changed to quadrilateral optimization,
the grid appearance of the board will change.
The 3D appearance will also be updated.
Now it is more convenient to change the grid type in the 3D and 2D windows.
In addition, the new version has optimized the wind control in the 3D window.
Wind control is an important interaction element.
It can perform natural movement of the fabric according to the airflow.
First, open the wind control in the 3D window to display the wind control.
There is a wind control.
You can use the wind control to change its position and direction by selecting the wind control.
Select the wind control.
You can activate it in the parameter editor.
At this time, we can open the simulation to check the effect.
If you want to add more wind controllers,
you can right-click on the current wind controller and click Copy.
Click Copy.
For the copied wind controller,
you can further adjust its position, wind direction, and wind strength.
If you want to delete it,
you can right-click on the wind controller and delete it.
Therefore, in the new version,
we can add more wind controllers
to show the mixed airflow from different directions.
In the new version,
you can set the conflict between the scene and the props
to ensure that there is a stable interaction between the clothes or props and the environment.
We can use the scene and props in Connect Sunshine,
and then add the clothes or props to the project.
In the previous version,
this scarf and necklace are used as an example.
When opening the simulation,
they will pass the props and drop them on the ground.
In the new version,
we can solve this problem
by opening the conflict between the scene and the props.
First, select the sofa.
In the model editor,
open the conflict below the specifications,
and then open the simulation.
You can see that the scarf and necklace
are stable on the sofa at this time.
At the same time,
you can adjust the conflict thickness
to set the distance between the props
and the props created by the template.
By using this function,
you can use these scene props more flexibly
to simulate a more realistic effect.
The following is the repair of the problem of the shadow of the folding board.
In the previous version,
there will usually be this unnatural shadow on the folding board.
Generally,
there will be such a shadow
on the center of the folding board where the balance is opened.
There will also be such a shadow
on the side of the folding board.
In the face of these situations,
users usually need to apply additional steps
to solve these problems,
such as removing the parallel relationship of the board,
reducing the particle diameter of the board, etc.
According to user feedback,
the new version has been optimized
and solved the problem of the shadow of the folding board.
There is no need for additional steps,
and the parallel editing relationship of the board can be maintained.
This optimization simplifies the operation steps of users
and is suitable for most clothing styles.
Next, we will start to explain the process of
the new functions related to virtual models.
First of all,
we will talk about the human face generator
that supports men and children.
In version 7.3.5.0,
we have introduced the function of the virtual model human face generator.
You can add key words or images
from the face characteristics of the virtual model.
In the previous version,
the function is limited to female models.
In this version,
you can use this function on the virtual model of men,
boys and girls.
Let's first import a male virtual model.
At present, I have added the file containing the male virtual model
in the 3D window.
In the virtual model on the main menu,
select the function of the human face generator.
As you can see now,
a new content has been added to the gender download menu.
You can find men, boys, girls and women.
Select men.
The options of age and race can be kept unchanged.
You can also select any age range from 10 to 80 years old.
You can also select race.
The working principle of the key word prompt
is the same as the working principle of any other AI function on Cloud.
Ensure that it is filled with words,
not long sentences.
Click on the image of the virtual model human face generator
at the top of the window.
You can also change the gender from here.
Click on the upload button to load the image.
Ensure that the image is a face-to-face photo,
without hair, glasses and shadows blocking the background.
It is recommended that the upload image resolution
is 1080 ppi or higher
to get a better effect.
This function is now also suitable for
male and female virtual models.
Note that this function is only suitable for
people aged 7 to 20 years old.
It is not suitable for male and female virtual models
under the age of 7 years old.
The function is still in the testing stage.
Therefore, we will continue to optimize this function
according to the feedback received in the future.
The next new function is about
supporting DAS Genesis 9 virtual models.
In our last 7.3 function update,
we released a DAS virtual model
that supports Genesis 8 virtual models.
Now, with the update of the new function in 2024,
the DAS virtual model's
automatic conversion function
has been expanded to support
Genesis 9 virtual models.
Next, let's take a look at the detailed operation process.
Go to the main menu of the virtual model,
then click on the automatic virtual model conversion.
It will pop up the window of the virtual model
that is automatically converted into a virtual model.
Click on the file and button next to the 3D model file
to open your virtual model.
In the window of the open file,
open the required virtual model,
select the DAS Genesis 9 virtual model
that is embedded in DAS,
and click on the open button.
A virtual model will be loaded into the 3D window.
Next, you can choose the gender of the virtual model.
If you want to do an automatic or custom conversion,
you can choose from the conversion options.
You can also choose the skin type.
On the left side of the skin type,
you can see different conversion types.
Here I will choose all three conversion types.
After the conversion, you will get three virtual models.
Choose to save the file path and change the name.
After completing the setting, click on the conversion.
Now, Cloud is going to start converting
the DAS virtual model into the Cloud virtual model.
After the conversion is completed,
you will see the window.
Open the folder of the file,
you can see the virtual model after the conversion.
Next, I would like to talk about
the configuration and skin type of the DAS Genesis 9 virtual model.
In the latest version of 2024,
we have provided a greater flexibility
from the definition of a virtual model.
The virtual model configuration
was originally used by a single virtual model.
Now, it has been expanded to
the self-defined option including a virtual model.
Select the virtual model in the folder,
open the file folder,
you can see the new virtual model.
From the file, you can see that,
Sasha, Melody and Oliver models
can be downloaded from Connect.
Download any child virtual model.
In the 3D window, click on the virtual model.
Then, in the attribute editor,
you will be able to see the skin type of the child virtual model.
You can switch between virtual models
in the download menu.
Switch the skin type of the girl virtual model.
You can also choose to switch between
the boy virtual model between Oliver and Melody.
Select the model configuration,
you can self-define each option.
Just like the previous operation
for adult virtual models.
You can also switch to
the eyebrows and lips of other virtual models.
If you want Sasha's eyebrows
to appear on Melody's face,
you can select Sasha
from the download menu next to the eyebrows.
You can also choose the integrated options
you want for each option.
For example, green,
plus or minus,
you can load the boy virtual model
and self-define the color of the hair,
skin, eyebrows, eyes and lips.
Note that if you have downloaded these virtual models before,
you must download them from Connect
to use this function.
So now we can use the virtual model
that self-defines children based on
our own aesthetics and preferences.
Next, we will explain
how to connect virtual models
to the arrangement point.
In this video,
we will explain how to connect virtual models
to the arrangement point.
In this function,
we will deeply study the enhancement function
of the arrangement point.
Not only can we satisfy the virtual model
but also expand to the model of Amano.
Let's take a look at the operation process.
First, open the arrangement point
in the 3D window of version 7.3.
Right-click the model of Amano
and select the virtual model and costume.
Use the positioning ball.
In version 7.3,
when you move the model of Amano,
the arrangement point will also move.
When you move the model of Amano,
This way, the whole operation
can simplify your workflow
to achieve the highest efficiency.
Next, we will explain
how to optimize virtual models,
arrangement board and arrangement point.
First, we will explain
how to use the arrangement point
in the 3D window of version 7.3.
First, we will explain
how to use the arrangement point
in the 3D window of version 7.3.
Starting from the latest version of
Clo 2024,
our users will add
an arrangement point and arrangement board
of multiple virtual models
in a single scene.
Now, let's take a look at the operation process.
Add multiple virtual models
to the scene,
open the arrangement point and arrangement board
of the virtual model.
As you can see,
both virtual models
On the left column, click on the virtual model, select the virtual model editor, and find the arrangement.
Select the virtual model you need from the selection menu of virtual models.
In the section below the arrangement panel, you can add or delete the arrangement panel.
You can also adjust the following parameters to change the arrangement panel position and size.
After adding the arrangement panel, you can add the arrangement point to the arrangement panel on the right side.
The arrangement point position can also be adjusted by parameters.
As the new version of 2024 is updated, the arrangement point on multiple virtual models can be arranged by multiple virtual models.
Next is the improvement of the human model of Connect.
In the Connect store, the human model of the five-faced virtual model has been updated.
Now their size can be edited.
This means that you can now use the virtual model editor in Cloud to edit these human models.
First, we make sure to log into the old Connect through the Cloud software.
Click Connect.
Select the virtual model.
Select the free option.
When you scroll down, you can see the five-faced human model or virtual model.
You can drag the male or female virtual model to the 3D window.
As you can see, this is the five-faced virtual model or human model provided by the Connect store.
Open the virtual model editor.
You can define the size of the virtual model according to your requirements.
This process is completely the same as the process of adjusting the Cloud virtual model.
Then I choose the weight as a parameter.
You can see that I can use the preset that can be used to change the model body shape.
If necessary, you can still save the size and reuse the size afterwards.
Now we can use these five-faced human models for testing.
Because their sizes are different.
Because their sizes can be edited.
Next, let's talk about the new features of the material.
First of all, the dual-head zipper.
Now, the 3D zipper tool not only provides single-head zipper, but also dual-head zipper.
This allows us to create more styles in a fast way.
For example, the double-head zipper jacket, the bag bag, and so on.
Next, let's take a look at the operation process.
First, select the zipper tool in the 3D window.
Install the zipper on the 3D or 2D version.
Press the button in the starting position.
At the end, double-click to complete one side.
Repeat the same steps on the other side.
After the zipper is added, simulate the fit of the zipper.
Press the zipper in the 3D window.
Come to the attribute editor.
The type is now single-head zipper.
Change the type to dual-head zipper.
There is a direction option below the type.
Now it is double-head.
This means that there are two zippers on both ends of the top and bottom of the plate.
If we change it to double-head, the two zippers will be in the middle of the entire zipper.
We can pull the zipper box or pull the zipper open.
Use the dual-head zipper to change the shape of the zipper and the zipper.
Now, let's take a look at the operation process.
We can change the shape of the zipper.
We can adjust the parameters according to the design.
Finally, I adjust the size and length of the zipper according to the effect I want.
Now, the zipper has been completed.
Double-head zipper is completed.
Next is to copy and paste when copying the template.
In the previous version, we only kept the button and OPJ copy and paste when copying the template.
When copying the template, the copy and paste will be lost.
In the new version, all the above materials can be kept.
Next, let's take a look at the operation process.
In this package, there is an Osmark zipper made with a sewing machine.
The zipper is still attached to the side of the zipper.
At present, this package only makes half of it.
In the previous version, when I copied these templates, you can see that the sewing machine and the side of the zipper are lost.
I need to copy the sewing machine separately and then add the side of the zipper again.
This takes some time.
Now, in the 2024 version, when I copy these templates,
I will keep the sewing machine and the side of the zipper.
Now I will copy the other half of the package as the back and arrange the position.
Then I will sew the side and bottom together and simulate it.
All the sewing machine and side of the zipper are still kept.
Then add a 3D zipper at the top of the package.
I added a zipper on the 2D version.
This will make it easier.
Click accurately.
The blue dot on the 3D window and the 2D window can help me identify the direction to start when adding another zipper.
After adding the 3D zipper and the hand I made in advance,
the Osmark zipper package is faster than before through the copy material function.
It is suitable for simple copy-paste operations,
such as sewing, pasting, line-stitching, and buttoning.
But at present, we still can't copy these templates.
This operation can only be done by connecting these templates and pasting them.
We can expect further improvements in the future version.
Next, we will make the template into an internal shape.
We can make the outline of the template into an internal line.
This will be very helpful for us to make a stamp or mark the location of the template.
Next, let's take a look at the operation process.
First, add a template to the skirt.
The template is a PNG template with no background.
Right-click the template and select the internal shape.
The internal line is created by the butterfly outline.
If there is a difference in detail between the internal line and the outline of the template,
you can adjust the line a little bit.
But this function can save a lot of time.
Next, we will make the outline of the skirt.
We can make the outline of the skirt.
Next, we can make the outline of the skirt.
If we want to make the outline of the skirt, we can adjust the line in the beautiful background.
panic
rapid
fast
is a new function update related to the model.
First, let's talk about the related UI of the old block library in the delete cloud.
As you may know,
in our last 7.3 update,
there are two block libraries,
the new block library and the block library.
Now, with the update of the new version of 2024,
the old block library editor mode and related UI have been deleted,
because many users use the old block library mode,
and the frequency is lower.
In the previous version,
the old block library is still retained on the left side of the library,
which leads to two block libraries in this position,
the new block library and the block library.
You can register and use the blocks in the block library compiler
displayed in the block library mode in the upper right corner.
In the new version of 2024,
the block library editor and the block library mode will all disappear,
and the new block library will be renamed the block library.
You can register and use the block library in the block library.
We have decided that
we will delete the old block library mode and related UI,
because many users use the old block library mode
after adding a new block library,
and the frequency will be lower.
Next, we will convert the old block library file
and upload it to the new block library.
With the update of the new version of 2024,
we will no longer support the old block library,
but the new version will add the old block library file,
convert and upload to the new block library function.
If you want to import the block library file created in the early version
and use it in the new version of 2024,
let's take a look at how the function is operated.
First, we will upload a block preview from the new block library in the 2024 version.
After uploading, we will simulate it.
Then we will import the ZBLC file.
This file is the component file stored in the early version,
and it is used to change the embroidery on the T-shirt file.
It is important to note that the structure of the component file created in the previous version
is the same as the component structure in the block library shown on the left side of the current 2024 new version.
Therefore, only the same position and the sewing line can be retained and converted.
Then, the ZBLC block file stored in the previous version
will be exported from the file window to the 3D window,
and the information window will pop up.
The ZBLC file has been actively loaded as a new block file.
You need to store it
to be able to use it as a complete new block file.
If you want to load a block file that is lower than the 2024 version again in the future,
and let the prompt no longer appear and be automatically used,
please click the option that is no longer displayed in the lower right corner.
Click Confirm to open the file.
You can see in the 3D window
that the short-term block file created in the previous version
has been converted into a new block file.
Click Edit Embroidery Tool,
and you can see that
the sewing line has also been sealed.
If you want to convert the sleeve version
to the new sleeve file in the new block file,
and import it to the new block file in the left-hand block box,
the ZMOD file
can be added by clicking the Add button in the sleeve file.
Since the old block file will no longer support the old block file
from the start of the 2024 version,
the old block file made with the old version
needs to be added to the new block box.
We will import the shirt block file made in the previous version.
It will prompt that the file will be added as a new block file.
The previously created part
needs to be converted and registered again through the upload method.
This process will be changed to an automatic conversion into a block in the future.
Next is to increase the option of setting the required folder as a default folder.
In version 7.3,
when the enterprise user uses the new block file,
they will often use a network drive,
such as OneDrive and Google Drive,
to share the folder.
However, the new block file does not allow users to change the default folder settings,
so we have to copy and paste it every time,
which makes it inconvenient to operate.
With the update of Cloud 2024,
we have added the option of setting the required folder as a default folder.
On the Cloud 2024 interface,
click on Settings on the main menu,
then on Settings,
then on User Identification,
then on Others,
then on Blockcharts,
and then on default folder.
Click on the file folder icon on the right,
and then in the selected folder window,
select the required folder as a default folder,
and then click on Close.
Next, let's check if the default folder has been successfully set.
Open the blockcharts.
When I want to add a new group in the blockcharts,
please click on the refresh button first,
and then click on Add Group.
In the open file window,
the default folder is displayed.
When we want to create a blockchart according to the current clothing style,
please click on the file on the main menu,
and then on Style.
The blockchart generator window will appear,
and the default folder will be listed in the search section.
Then click on the Add button.
In the open file window,
the default folder is displayed.
The above display indicates that we have successfully set the default folder.
With the update of Cloud 2024,
we have added the option to set the data folder as the default folder.
This will make it easier for us to create blockchart files,
and share blockchart files internally.
Next, I would like to talk about the new function update related to rendering,
which is to be able to save the rotating animation with a transparent background.
In the previous version,
due to the inability to select the transparency option,
the software was unable to render the JIF rotating images and animations with a transparent background.
From the start of the Cloud 2024 version,
you can select the transparency option,
and save the JIF rotating images and animations with a transparent background.
Next, let's take a look at the specific operation process.
In the interface of the new 2024 version,
click on Render on the main menu.
In the rendering window,
click on the image video attribute.
In the image video of the attribute editor,
select Rotate Image or Animation.
Then, save the JIF.
In the background column,
find the transparency option.
As shown,
the transparency can be selected after selecting Rotate Image or Animation.
It is no longer gray and unselectable.
After setting the attribute,
click on Final Render.
Finally, a JIF rotating animation that can be rotated will be generated.
Open the JIF file completed,
and check the final effect.
This function allows us to save the JIF rotating animation with a transparent background.
It is convenient for us to display the rotating animation on different platforms.
Finally, let's talk about the color update.
From the start of the Cloud 7.3 update,
we have improved the color function and structure,
making it easier to adjust and set the color.
Now, you can apply different material and materials with different attributes to each color,
such as fabric,
and when you apply each material to the board,
you can choose how to apply it to each color.
Next, let's learn through some examples
how to apply the improved color function.
Example 1. Color operation process.
Start by creating a color from the beginning.
Open the editor in the main menu,
click Color,
click Color window,
click Color editor,
click the plus sign in the upper right corner of the window,
add color,
create a different color for this JIF.
First, when you apply the same material,
you want to apply a different color for each color type.
Next, let's change the color of the second JIF to the fabric color of the JIF.
First, select the second JIF.
Then, select the Baseball GK fabric applied to the JIF.
In the color of the attribute editor on the right,
change the color of the fabric,
then click Apply and close.
Click the update in the upper left corner of the color editor window
to check the effect of the color after the color change.
If you want to keep the color you changed,
and only apply different materials to the designated color,
the following operations will meet this requirement.
First, click Color 2,
which is the third color.
If you want to apply different materials to the color,
first add the material to the object window.
Double click the JIF,
material,
select these two materials,
add them to the object window separately.
Then, in the 3D window,
select the Baseball GK.
Click Apply to the selected version of the current one,
or drag the material directly to the selected version.
It will show the option window for applying to the color.
You can choose among them how to apply the material to the color.
Select the first option,
and click Apply to the current color.
Then, click OK to apply.
After clicking the update in the upper left corner,
you can see the JIF in Color 2.
The material of the Baseball GK in Color 2
has been changed to the state you want.
The material of the Baseball GK in Color A and Color 1
and the color remain unchanged.
Only the material of Color 2 has been changed.
Under the current color,
select the material block used in the Baseball GK.
Make it stand out.
If you drag another material to the material block,
it will automatically and only apply to the current color.
The effect and application are the same as the current color.
You don't need to select it in the selected window.
Then click Update to confirm the effect of the color change.
If you want to change the same material type to all colors,
and it is convenient to immediately modify the related material type in the future,
we can see the following operations.
Next, we will apply the leather fabric used in the JIF.
The leather fabric used in the JIF has been changed to the patterned fabric.
First, select all embroidered panels in the 3D window.
Then drag the new embroidered fabric added to the 5D window
to the embroidered panel.
In the color window applied to the spring ball,
select the second one to apply to all colors.
You can also change the color.
Then click OK.
Click Update.
You can see that
all the embroidered panels have been changed to patterned fabric.
In the list below,
click on a new sleeve panel.
The newly applied fabric type will show up.
After selecting the new sleeve panel,
select and change the color in the attribute editor on the right.
Then click Update.
You can see that all the embroidered panels have been changed to the same color.
In addition,
if you want to apply the same material type
to two designated colors,
instead of the current three visible colors,
you can quickly change them.
You can see the following operations.
In the color editor,
while pressing Shift,
click on the patterned fabric in color 1 and 2.
Then drag the fabric in the 5D window on the right
to the selected object.
Click Update to check.
You can see that only color 1 and 2 have been changed.
If you want to change the color,
the change should only be applied to color 1 and 2.
Here, the patterned fabric has been linked.
If you want to cancel the link between the two fabrics
and edit color 2 separately,
you can click on the fabric type in the color editor
on the right.
Click Unlink all colors,
and you can cancel the link.
Then,
modify the color of the fabric block of color 2 separately.
As you can see,
after canceling the link,
you can change the color of the fabric separately.
Finally,
if you want to use the same type of fabric
in the selected fabric,
you can also modify the color and type of fabric
of the designated flag separately.
You can see the following operations.
First,
select the sleeve fabric in the 3D window.
Drag the Baseball GT Sleeves fabric
to the selected sleeve fabric.
Then,
select the third option
in the selected window.
Use all colors.
Cancel the link to change the color separately.
Click OK.
Select the fabric block in the third color.
In the attribute editor on the right,
change the color and click update.
You can see that the three colors of the sleeve fabric
have been changed,
and only the third designated color
has been changed separately.
If you have a fixed option,
you can save and use them to keep them.
In this way,
you don't have to choose them every time
when setting up.
If you want to keep the selected option,
please choose to apply the current setting
to the bottom of the color window.
If you want to change the option to save
to other options,
or want to play out the application
to the color window again,
you can change it in the setting
in the user definition.
The specific location is in the main menu,
setting,
and then click OK.
You can see that the color of the fabric
has been changed.
In the main menu,
set,
user definition,
other,
color,
or color editor window,
click the set color option in the upper right corner.
If you keep the current setting
closed in the option,
every time you apply the fabric
to the designated version of the color,
this will pop up
and apply to the color window.
If you choose to keep the current setting
option,
click any of the options.
When applying the fabric
to the designated version,
the selected option will be activated.
Next,
I will explain the compatibility
of the new version
with the previous version
of the color file created.
When using the new version software
to load the 7.3 version
or the project file
processed earlier than the 7.3 version,
the window will pop up.
Because before the 7.3 version,
even if each color
uses the same fabric,
these fabrics are also
individually applied to each color
and are not identified as individual fabrics.
However,
from 7.3 and the new 2024 version,
this function has been improved.
If each color uses the same fabric,
it can be identified as the same fabric.
Therefore,
the window can choose to apply the fabric
to one of the two structures.
The function can be improved
and it is convenient to calculate
the total amount of single fabrics
used in each color in the cloud in the future.
If you consider this possibility,
it is recommended that you click Yes
to enter them into the same structure.
Click Yes
to enter the same structure.
to load the color file
and then select the left side of the object window
to display all the colors
to check all the fabric types used.
Because the Yes option is selected in the front,
you can see that
the same fabric types used
have been linked
and are loaded into the object window
as the same fabric.
If the CFAB fabric file
is created in the version before 7.3,
the color information will be included in the fabric file.
However,
it has been improved from the new version.
A fabric file only contains one kind of fabric information.
If you want to load and use the CFAB fabric file
created in the version before 7.3,
and the fabric file contains the color information,
please put the CFAB file into the object window.
Then a new window will appear,
as shown on the screen.
If you click Yes,
all the colors used in the fabric
will be loaded into the object window
as a new fabric file
and as a separate CFAB file.
If you click No,
the object selected when saving the CFAB
will be loaded as a single fabric file.
If you open the fabric file
in the existing fabric
through the attribute editor
or directly drag it into the CFAB,
it will be replaced
with the single fabric
selected when saving.
It will not pop out of the window.
By updating the text,
the fabric color has been improved,
and the working method is more diversified and convenient.
We can use the fabric color editor more efficiently.
Next,
we will explain the new features of Closet.
After the 3D file is completed,
users can upload it to our cloud platform Closet
for further cooperation.
If you are a new Closet user,
you can often explore its functions
on the Closet website.
This year,
we have added more functions to Closet
to enhance the seamless communication
and workflow of your 3D assets.
Next,
we will take a look at the specific operation process
to enhance the seamless communication
and workflow of your 3D assets.
Next,
we will take a look at
the new function operation process of Closet.
Closet in the cloud software
Users can upload the finished 3D clothing
seamlessly to Closet.
Click the Closet button in the upper right corner
to open the upload page.
Then,
select the location,
which is a specific studio.
Then,
click the upload button.
After uploading the file,
users can share the file
to others on the right.
You can choose
the person you want to share
or enter the email.
After selecting the whole line,
click Share.
Now,
users can also share the file
with a group of people
through the team function.
Select Group 1.
Select their whole line,
and share it.
After completion,
the group of collaborators
will receive a legal notice.
Users can manage the notice board,
team management.
Here,
you can specify the team label.
Click Create New Team.
Fill in the relevant information of the team
and the email address of the team member.
Click Create.
Then,
the team's creation is completed.
when other users
check the files in the content page,
Closet provides a 3D real-time viewfinder
to check the structure of the machine.
It includes different display options,
similar to Closet,
such as the text surface
and the semi-transparent surface.
This season,
Closet also added a hard drive
to the viewfinder
to help users
check the appearance of the clothing.
In addition to the 3D viewfinder,
users can also
check the basic information of the document
in the left area.
For example,
the name of the style,
the name of the product,
and the name of the product.
In addition,
the name of the style,
the name of the product,
and so on.
If this 3D file
creates a certain clothing
in Closet,
for example,
the top garment in the company's pants,
users can use the link content
to check which clothing
is created in the file,
that is,
the content of the file,
to better track and manage
your digital assets.
After the users check the structure
of the 3D clothing sample,
they can use comments
to share their feedback.
For example,
users can add logo tags
to the print on the comments.
They can drag the relevant images
to a certain position
as a copy of the comments.
After the comments are posted,
other users can preview them.
Note that if necessary,
users can use the viewfinder
to mark the comments in the 3D window.
Through collaboration,
users can modify the file
and upload the latest version
to Closet.
After the file is completed,
if users do not have time
to render in Closet,
they can render in Closet.
The rendering settings
are basically the same as in Closet,
such as resolution,
rendering quality, and so on.
After Closet is updated,
users can choose
to render the file
as a rotating image
and save it as a .jf
or video format.
After rendering the file,
you can preview it
through the screenshot
on the left-hand side of the single machine.
Then,
you can use the button
on the bottom right corner
to download the rotating image
or video.
Here is the video
after the download.
Through the above steps,
users can cooperate
and design comments
with others.
In the next few weeks,
more new functions
of Closet
will be released.